Nanasaheb Yadav



nanayadav33@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/nanasahebn



+91 9970673015



https://github.com/nanasaheb-yadav

Summary

4 years of total experience, with 2+ years of experience in Python Development.

Highly adept at Python Development, UIPath Automation, Web Automation, Web Scraping, Testing and Deployment, Agile Methodologies.

Received Hall of Fame and Star Performer award while working at Capgemini.

Experience



Python Developer

Capgemini

Jan 2019 - Present (2 years 6 months +)

- Collaborated as integral part of team of 6 Python and 4 UIPath developers.
- Implemented 4+ software BOT's based on client needs using Python and UIPath.
- Worked on RPA, Web Automation, Web Scrapping, ServiceNow Automation, Data Analysis and Reporting.
- Developed 20+ use cases using Python, UIPath and Databases (Oracle/MySQL) in 2 years.
- Adapted Agile software development process and DevOps.
- Compiled websites data for competitive analysis by performing web scrapping and data analysis in python.
- Preprocess data and created reports using pandas, matplotlib, numpy, beautifulsoup libraries.

Senior Analyst

Capgemini

Dec 2017 - Dec 2018 (1 year 1 month)

- Experience building dashboards to show insights of different portfolios, dashboards, and detailed reports to higher management.
- Comfortable with accessing SQL databases and writing queries.
- Automated deployment process of 4000+ stores POS using Python and Power shell scripting.
- Performed functional and technical test execution activities as per test plan.
- Coordinated with development team to create test plans for enhancements and fixes on applications
- Led team of 3 people
- Remote POS Application and Packages deployment on 4000+ Starbucks stores.
- Awarded by Rising Star Award in 2018.



Analyst

Capgemini

Apr 2017 - Nov 2017 (8 months)

- Completed Java 8 training (JEE) in organization.
- Provided Level 2 support to Java projects.
- Hands-on Java/J2EE programming and diagnostic experience

Education



Savitribai Phule Pune University

BE, Information Technology 2013 - 2016



SVERI's College of Engineering, Pandharpur

Diploma, Information Technology 2010 - 2013

Licenses & Certifications



Building Web Applications in Django - Coursera



Web Application Technologies and Django - Coursera



Introduction to Git and GitHub - Coursera



Web Scraping with Python + BeautifulSoup - Coursera



Crash Course on Python - Coursera



Agile Software Development - Coursera



Automation Engineer Practitioner Certified - Capgemini Academy

Skills

Python (Programming Language) • Web Scraping • Databases • Agile Methodologies • REST APIs • Azure DevOps • Robotic Process Automation (RPA) • Git • Django REST Framework • Data Analysis

Honors & Awards



Star Performer Award - Capgemini

2019



Hall of Fame Award - Capgemini

2020